Guide to the Edward Robb Ellis Papers ca. 1902-1998 MSS.068
Fales Library and Special Collections
Edward Robb Ellis Papers
ca. 1902-1998
Fales Library and Special Collections
MSS.068
60 Linear Feet (53 boxes)
The bulk of the collection is a continuous diary kept from 1927 up until Edward Robb Ellis' death in 1998. The diary includes handwritten and typed entries as well as photographs and correspondence and consists of bound volumes and loose pages. Also included in the collection are clippings arranged into subject files, book typescripts and audio and visual media.
Provenance
Papers donated by Edward Robb Ellis in 1993.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Edward Robb Ellis was born in 1911 in Kewanee, Illinois. He began writing his diary in 1927 and continued writing until his death in 1998. Determined to be a reporter, Edward Ellis attended the journalism program at the University of Missouri and in 1934 took his first job as a professional reporter for the New Orleans Associated Press office. In this position he covered the events of the Great Depression and the political career of Huey Long. After two years in New Orleans, he moved to Oklahoma City and became a journalist for the Oklahoma City Times covering New Deal offices and programs. As part of this position he reported on the Oklahoma Federal Symphony Orchestry, which was funded by the Works Progress Administration. Through this assignment Eddie met and fell in love with the principal violinist, Leatha Sparlin. They married in 1939 and moved to Peoria, Illinois where he worked for the Journal-Transcript. The couple then moved to Chicago where Eddie worked for The Daily News. Their daughter Sandra Gail Ellis was born on December 28, 1942.
Shortly after Sandra's birth, Eddie Ellis became aware that a previous diagnosis of a hernia was incorrect. He anticipated being drafted and consequently sought a commission in the navy. He was unable to receive one due to his low weight. As a result, he joined the navy and reported to training on November 7, 1942. Because diary keeping was prohibited in the armed forced he changed the format of the diary from private entries to letters to his wife and daughter. Ellis detested boot camp, upon finishing he was appointed editor of the navy hospital newspaper called The Bedside Examiner. He used his position to publish editorials promoting enlisted people's rights as well as critiques of war. After basic training he was stationed in Okinawa where he continued to publish a newspaper, this time explicitly to improve the sailors' morale. Four months later the war ended and he returned to the United States. His wife requested a divorce, which he granted the following month and returned to work at The Daily News in Chicago.
Ellis did not fit in under the new management at the newspaper in Chicago however, and he soon left for New York to work at the World Telegram. Ellis loved New York City deeply and would remain in the City for the rest of his life. There he met and married Ruth Kraus. They had an exceptionally happy marriage. After 15 years at the World Telegram Ellis quit after a disagreement with a city editor. He used his time unemployed to write several books, often with Ruth's help. He published four A Diary of the Century, Epic of New York, Echoes of Distant Thunder, and A Nation in Torment.
Ruth died suddently of a heart attack in 1965. Eddie Ellis went on to have several extended romances, one with June Morgan and another with Selma Pezaro. Although Eddie was not a strong presence in his daughter's childhood, he and Sandy became close in her adulthood, writing numerous letters and challenging each other intellectually. He also forged mentoring relationships with other diarists, usually as a result of interviews and through the publication of parts of the diary in A Diary of the Century. His reputation as a diarist led Letts of London to create a diary modeled on his recommendations called "The Ellis Diary".
Edward Robb Ellis died in 1998 of emphysema. Throughout his career as a reporter, Eddie Ellis interviewed numerous political and cultural celebrities including Eleanor Roosevelt, Irving Berlin, Grace Kelley and Herbert Hoover. The diary records his impressions of these famous personalities. Ellis was equally fascinated by the experiences and perceptions of ordinary people. He prided himself on his curiosity and eagerness to learn and considered himself what Shakespeare called "a snapper-up of unconsidered trifles." The diary is a collection of those trifles and Eddie Ellis's attempt, as Pete Hamill writes in the introduction to A Diary of the Century "to freeze time" and reflect on himself and humanity.
Scope and Content Note
The collection is comprised of a continuous diary spanning over sixty years. The diary includes written and typed entries as well as personal correspondence, photographs, magnetic audiotape, Super 8 home movies as well as video and audiocassettes. Also included in the diary are book typescripts, subject files and scrapbooks of newspaper clippings covering a wide range of topics. All materials except media are described to the box-level only.
Arrangement
Series I: Diary The diary contains bound volumes of handwritten and typed entries as well as loose entries, newspaper clippings, photographs and correspondence. The diary is arranged chronologically by year with larger documents in four oversize boxes.
Series II: Subject Files Subject files contain newspaper and magazine clippings grouped by Edward Ellis and organized alphabetically with larger items located in five oversize boxes. Two very large items are located in the map case.
Series III: Book Typescripts Series three contains manuscripts for completed and partially completed books including fiction and non-fiction works. Typescripts are arranged alphabetically by title. This series also includes one oversize box.
Series IV: Media This series contains magnetic audiotapes and cassettes of interviews and correspondence as well as mounted color transparencies, videocassettes and 8mm double film. Media is arranged chronologically with undated materials at the end of the sequence. Access copies are not yet available for this material.
Missing Title
Series I: Diary
Series II: Subject Files
Series III: Book Typescripts
Series IV: Media
Oversize - Series I: Diary
Oversize - Series II: Subject Files
Oversize - Series III: Book Typescripts
Photographs; Chicago (Ill.); Audiotapes.; New York (N.Y.); Diaries; Caricatures.; Oklahoma City (Okla.); Peoria (Ill.); Clippings (information artifacts); Ellis, Edward Robb |x Diaries.; Color transparencies.; Videocassettes.; United States |x History |y 20th century.; Journalists |z United States |v Diaries.; Kewanee (Ill.); Okinawa (Japan); Typescripts.; Portraits.; New York World-Telegram; New Orleans Item; Peoria Journal-Transcript; Oklahoma City Times; Emelio, Shine; Emelio, Sandra Gail Ellis; Letts of London; Emelio, Victor; Wind, Lucy; Sparlin, Leatha; Pezaro, Selma Seskin; University of Missouri; United Press International. Chicago; Emelio, Orion; Ellis, Ruth Kraus; Ellis, Edward Robb
- Series I: Diary
  Scope and Contents note
  The diary contains bound volumes of handwritten and typed entries as well as loose entries, newspaper clippings, photographs and correspondence. The diary is arranged chronologically by year with larger documents in four oversize boxes.
  - 1902-1933 (Box 1, Folder data_value_missing_4181bb6a9a469c81147a6922fcbd6e58)
  - 1933-1938 (Box 2, Folder data_value_missing_a8a512ed0c3c8c0d0629dc2072afa2cf)
  - 1938-1946 (Box 3, Folder data_value_missing_7821249ee80c041586a813fcbbd766f6)
  - 1946-1950 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_719c25774e44cb2de01c226b750f440b)
  - 1950-1953 (Box 5, Folder data_value_missing_355601dcface6619706e7d1402b0600e)
  - 1954-1956, 19954-1956 (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_82b45164f1a0f9e59c715730364cc90f)
  - 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_ee50328717de4f1ca232701108e205bf)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_cffd9c5089ef7b39d3b9f3c02dee9287)
  - 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_6c4f32b653867ea0b61b1ec83cf901cc)
  - 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_d53db0942a31668b3c5af806b9dff7d9)
  - 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_ee7eb6fa5d109a6402f7fd4d21099d40)
  - 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder data_value_missing_4bba1b6aa24f9d4fd23899b2499740ca)
  - 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder data_value_missing_ed4d37379e04b0dde08037cc660a68b6)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder data_value_missing_e4330820f2ec9d982e2fafc5c88cb444)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder data_value_missing_b5abcfaf50aca529ef488f991f3d3328)
  - 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder data_value_missing_9277c4a9658298a20a909eea2bb87538)
  - 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_957fdb9569a19a39b918ad91fea7c579)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder data_value_missing_6888d2d2191a276e031239a664bfb656)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder data_value_missing_fc6d6774118a5f9ecbbbd14db1996817)
  - 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_c9eb837bf8113d29da0ab0a36a101901)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_9d866ee3b7c37b6628933ef7e89cd7cc)
  - 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_bbd2f4e315525f7d0331fadc6c0d4b04)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_f068397d8bde4d8e9cda27dbba021ccc)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder data_value_missing_4cdc2391253b63a58f3b4414a1d27b49)
  - 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder data_value_missing_541334c36c0a184e6da62136c191e322)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_d7dd6fb1fb01e470033d1fe6051af012)
  - 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_80edb3472b5791a2ba794c6f5b745d57)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_2a73a29f469b4217ba6bfa8f64cd7a11)
  - 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_4a54185c001d585d47248a1cc6a658f0)
  - 1995 (Box 30, Folder data_value_missing_e603680db6cbd6b56b9e0ca4148fb1d9)
  - 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder data_value_missing_b7fbe9061d2bfeb6aab0df2ee9d9b89c)
  - 1998-Miscellaneous undated (Box 32, Folder data_value_missing_e70a70612aec0382671e148b91447db4)
- Series II: Subject Files
  Subject files contain newspaper and magazine clipping grouped by Edward Ellis and organized alphabetically by first letter with larger items located in five oversize boxes. Two very large items are located in the map case.
  - A-B, undated (Box 32, Folder data_value_missing_b866c77a6eb40b6888493eca237de2c5)
  - B-I, undated (Box 33, Folder data_value_missing_87fb19e75e5543f5022cfa5d1dfc3c38)
  - K-W, undated (Box 34, Folder data_value_missing_5117bc0a7f79f112866eda3ec0d8614e)
  - W-Miscellaneous subjects, undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_e28234ea97cb24a8449acaef0a91412b)
- Series III: Book Typescripts
  Series three contains manuscripts for completed and partially completed books including fiction and non-fiction works. Typescripts are arranged alphabetically by title. This series also includes one oversize box.
  - Diary of a Reporter and Diary of a Century, undated (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_ecd065056d8351de0ec97f3d31e7564d)
  - Diary of a Century, Echoes of a Distant Thunder, The Ellis Diary and Epic of New York, undated (Box 36, Folder data_value_missing_c79bc71d25cca48519053cde197045a7)
  - Epic of New York, Erika, Harbor of New York, A Nation in Torment, The Old Man Turns On, A Sexual History of the United States, and Steve, undated (Box 37, Folder data_value_missing_d373d987add8ac724215934e05d14266)
  - Steve, Traitor Within, The Watchdogs, and Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated (Box 38, Folder data_value_missing_1c10dff321cb0e8cb00c6aee0eef5b81)
  - Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated (Box 39, Folder data_value_missing_6ffed219ada181ba80b1cbbf5925547b)
- Series IV: Media
  This series contains magnetic audiotapes and audiocassettes of interviews and correspondence as well as mounted color transparencies, videocassettes and 8mm double film. This series is arranged chronologically with undated materials at the end of the sequence.
  - #1 Mother's visit to N.Y., 1955, ID: 068.0001 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0001)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    Double 8mm film, Kodachrome, safety color film, 25 feet
  - Kewanee - Processed, December 13, 1956, circa 1956; ID: 068.0002 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0002)
  - Emerson, Fontaines, Friseman, Steve Seskin, July-August 1958, ID: 068.0003 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0003)
    Double 8mm film, Kodachrome color safety film, 25 ft.
  - Geo? Allen Boat, Aug. 1958, ID: 068.0004 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0004)
    Double 8mm film, Kodachrome color safety film,
  - Labor Day 1958, Moira and Don Johnston, ID: 068.0005 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0005)
    Double 8mm film, Kodachrome color movie film, 25 feet
  - Iris and Bill Rassieur, Kay and Bob Burton, Sept. 1958, ID: 068.0006 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0006)
    Double 8mm Kodachrome color movie film, 25 feet
  - July 1959, Cologne - the Rhine - Joel and Joyce, ID: 068.0007 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0007)
    Double 8mm, Kodachrome color safety film, 25 feet
  - Sunset and Sandy in NY, 1959, ID: 068.0008 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0008)
    Super 8mm film, Kodak
  - #1 Washington, D.C., July 19-20, 1960, ID: 068.0009 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0009)
  - Geo. Allen on Terrace Mary Frishone, July 1961 to Danford [Fla] w Lubells, ID: 068.0010 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0010)
    Double 8mm daylight Kodachrome, 25 feet
  - May 1962, San Juan #3, ID: 068.0011 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0011)
    Double 8mm artificial light Kodachrome, 25 feet
  - 1962- Selma Maggie- Terrace, Macy Fireworks, Fire on NJ Pier, ID: 068.0012 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0012)
    Double 8mm Kodachrome film, 25 feet
  - #1 Aruba, May 1962 also labeled #4 Aruba on edge, ID: 068.0013 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0013)
    Double 8mm Daylight Kodachrome, 25 feet
  - Ellis Isle June, 1962, ID: 068.0014 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0014)
    [Super 8mm?] Kocachrome color movie film
  - July 1963, Jack [unknown] Maggie Thomas South terrace, ID: 068.0015 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0015)
    Double 8mm color movie film, 25 feet
  - Sandy Ellis in N.Y., Oct. 1963, ID: 068.0016 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0016)
    Double 8mm Dynachrome color movie film, reversal type, 25 feet
  - April '64, Party at Jacks- Eddie, Ruth, Joan opposite side labeled "Burtons film", 1964; ID: 068.0017 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0017)
    [Some sort of 8mm] Kodachrome movie film
  - Summer 1964, Sailing vessels, Riverside Park and point, ID: 068.0018 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0018)
    Double 8mm Dynachrome color movie film for Daylight, 25 feet
  - Empty canister. Kodachrome II double 8mm., ca. 1966 (Box 50)
    none
  - Unprocessed, ca. 1966; ID: 068.0019 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0019)
    Unprocessed Double 8mm Dynachrome daylight film, 25 feet
  - Annapurna, ca. 1957; ID: 068.0020 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0020)
    Double 8mm Kodachrome color safety film, 25 feet
  - incomplete, ca. 1957; ID: 068.0021 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0021)
    Unprocessed Double 8mm Kodachrome color safety film for 8mm magazine cameras.
  - Dan Mahoney, May 4, 1961, ID: 068.0022 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0022)
    Magnetic Audio tape, Scotch brand .25 inch, 300 feet
  - Dan Mahoney, May 4, 1961, ID: 068.0023 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0023)
    Magnetic Audio Tape, Scotch brand .25 inch, 300 feet
  - Olga Paracka and space shoot, May 5, 1961, ID: 068.0024 (Box 50, Media ID: 068.0024)
    Magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand, .25 inch, 300 ft.
  - Jane Fisher, May 5, 1961, ID: 068.0025 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0025)
    Magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand, .25 inch, 300 feet
  - Mrs. Jane Fisher, May 5, 1961, ID: 068.0026 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0026)
    Magnetic audiotape
  - Bob Ruark- Hotel Elysee, Wed May 10, 1961, ID: 068.0027 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0027)
    Magnetic audiotape, High fidelity recording tape, approx. 225 feet
  - Larry Smits, May 15, 1961 Done, ID: 068.0028 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0028)
    Magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand, .25 inch 300 feet
  - one side only, Larry Smits, May 15, 1961 Done, ID: 068.0029 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0029)
    Magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand .25 inch 300 feet
  - May 16, 1961, Roy Jones, ID: 068.0030 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0030)
    Magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand, .25 inch 300 feet, 3.75 speed
  - May 16, 1961, Jim Farley, Coke record, Sherman Brown, ID: 068.0031 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0031)
  - Camille Street, May 22, 1961, ID: 068.0032 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0032)
    Magnetic audiotape, high fidelity recording tape, approx. 225 feet
  - Bob Chernoff, May 22, 1961, ID: 068.0033 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0033)
    Magnetic audiotape, high fidelity, approx 225 feet.
  - Bob Chernoff and Camilee Street, May 22 1961, ID: 068.0034 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0034)
    Magnetic audiotape, high fidelity, approximately 225 feet
  - Earle B. Greene, May 23, 1961, ID: 068.0035 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0035)
    magnetic audiotape, high fidelity, approx 225 feet
  - Earle B. Greene, May 23, 1961, ID: 068.0036 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0036)
    Magnetic audiotape, high fidelity, approx. 225 feet
  - Lola Leonard, May 28, 1961, ID: 068.0037 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0037)
  - Adela St. Johns, June 1, 1961, ID: 068.0038 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0038)
  - Adela St. Johns, June 1, 1961, ID: 068.0039 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0039)
  - Larry Smits, June 11, 1961, ID: 068.0040 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0040)
    Magnetic audiotape, Dictape, 300 feet, .25 inch
  - Paul Snell, June 12, 1961, ID: 068.0041 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0041)
  - Paul Snell, June 12, 1961, ID: 068.0042 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0042)
  - Ned Moss, Hollywood, June 12, 1961, ID: 068.0043 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0043)
  - Eddie Hoff Hollywood, June 14, 1961, ID: 068.0044 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0044)
    Magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand .25 inch, 300 feet
  - Emilie Holden Joe Pasternak Hollywood, June 14, 1961, ID: 068.0045 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0045)
  - Mike Romanoff, June 14, 1961, Message to Ruthie from Sandy, Joe Pasternak, Emilie Holden, ID: 068.0046 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0046)
  - Milburn McCarty, Jack Whitney, July 19, 1961, ID: 068.0047 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0047)
    Magnetic audiotape, Dictape .25 inch, 300 feet
  - Larry Smits, July 11, 1961 done- but other side blank, ID: 068.0048 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0048)
  - Margaret Ray, July 14, 1961, ID: 068.0049 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0049)
    Magnetic audiotape, 300 feet
  - Ed Weimer, July 18 1961, ID: 068.0050 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0050)
    Magnetic audiotape, Dictape, .25 inch, 300 feet
  - Ed Weimer, July 18, 1961, ID: 068.0051 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0051)
  - Bob Harron, July 21, 1961, ID: 068.0052 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0052)
  - Leo Dolan, July 24, 1961, ID: 068.0053 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0053)
    Magnetic audiotape, Dictape, .25 inch 300 feet
  - Leo Dolan, July 24, 1961, ID: 068.0054 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0054)
  - Rickenbacker, Aug. 2, 1961 Audrey Pearce, ID: 068.0055 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0055)
  - Joe Copps - one side only, Aug. 12, 1961, ID: 068.0056 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0056)
  - Joe Copps, Aug. 12, 1961, ID: 068.0057 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0057)
  - Joe Copps, Aug. 12, 1961, ID: 068.0058 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0058)
  - Audrey Pierce, Aug. 13, 1961, ID: 068.0059 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0059)
  - W. Averell Harrimar, Aug. 27, 1961, ID: 068.0060 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0060)
  - Joe Copps, Sept 15, 1961, ID: 068.0061 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0061)
  - Joe Copps, Sept 16, 1961, ID: 068.0062 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0062)
  - Arthur Godfrey, Sept. 26, 1961, ID: 068.0063 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0063)
  - Morton Downey, Sept 28, 1961, ID: 068.0064 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0064)
  - Joe E. Lewis and Sherman Bellingsley, Sun. Oct 1, 1961, ID: 068.0065 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0065)
  - Mike Wallace Show - PM East Wed., Oct 4, 1961 and Roseanne Bagrion, ID: 068.0066 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0066)
  - Nov. 8, 1963, Ron Tomm (just one side used); Ann Loring, Nov. 11, 1963-other side, ID: 068.0067 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0067)
    Magnetic audiotape, unknown tape brand or length
  - Larry #2, Nov. 11, 1963, ID: 068.0068 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0068)
  - Audrey Peters of Love and LIfe, Dec. 16, 1964, ID: 068.0069 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0069)
    Magnetic audiotape, Ferrodynamics, .25 inch, 600 feet
  - Bonnie Bedelia, November 30, 1964 and Roy Winsor, Dec. 1, 1964, ID: 068.0070 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0070)
    Magnetic audiotape, Ferrodynamics, .25 inch 600 feet
  - Luis Sanguino, Jan 18, 1965, ID: 068.0071 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0071)
    Magnetic audiotape, Ferrodynamics, unknown length
  - Luis Sanguino, Jan 18, 1965, ID: 068.0072 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0072)
  - Tunney Dempsey - double speed, undated; ID: 068.0073 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0073)
  - Dempsey one side only, undated; ID: 068.0074 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0074)
    Magnetic audiotape, audiotape brand, 300 feet
  - unlabeled content, sent to J.T. Ellis Jr. in Chicago by E. Ellis in, New YorK, undated; ID: 068.0075 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0075)
    Magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand, unknown length
  - David Round, undated; ID: 068.0076 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0076)
    Magnetic audiotape, Burgess.25 inch, 150 feet
  - Sam Pryor, Bernard Giurbel one side done, undated; ID: 068.0077 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0077)
    Magnetic audiotape, Super-thin, audiotape brand, 300 feet
  - Used by Jack Waugh - Edward Ellis World-Telegram, undated; ID: 068.0078 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0078)
  - Margaret Ray, undated; ID: 068.0079 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0079)
    Magnetic audiotape, Super-Thin Audiotape brand, 300 feet
  - Bob Harron, undated; ID: 068.0080 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0080)
  - 1 and 2, undated; ID: 068.0081 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0081)
    Magnetic audiotape, Dicatpe, .25 inch, 300 feet
  - Only bit of one side used, undated; ID: 068.0082 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0082)
    Magnetic audiotape, Super-thin Audiotape brand, 300 feet
  - Mike Wallace, undated; ID: 068.0083 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0083)
  - Milburn McCarty and Sam Pryor, undated; ID: 068.0084 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0084)
    Magnetic audiotape, unknown brand and length
  - Hal Thurber, Tom Johnston, Joe Dienbart, undated; ID: 068.0085 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0085)
  - Mrs. Gable and Eddie Hoff, Jack Benny, undated; ID: 068.0086 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0086)
  - Dorothy Pearlman and Chas. Ward, undated; ID: 068.0087 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0087)
    Magnetic audiotape, Super-thin audiotape brand, 300 feet
  - Joe Copps re: Ford, undated; ID: 068.0088 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0088)
  - Ross Young and Jennie Sweeting, undated; ID: 068.0089 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0089)
    Magnetic audiotape,High Fidelity, Approx 225 feet
  - Joe Copps, Sept 16., undated; ID: 068.0090 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0090)
    Magnetic audiotape,Scotch brand, .25 inch 300 feet
  - untitled, undated; ID: 068.0091 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0091)
    Magnetic audiotape, Ferrodynamics, 600 feet
  - Norburt Wheeler and Mrs. Pearlman, undated; ID: 068.0092 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0092)
  - Mrs. Gale, Hal Thurber, one side only, undated; ID: 068.0093 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0093)
  - Hal Thurber, Done, undated; ID: 068.0094 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0094)
  - Unlabeled, undated; ID: 068.0095 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0095)
    Magnetic audiotape,Dictape, 300 feet
  - Sullivan, Mrs. Nichols, Done, undated; ID: 068.0096 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0096)
    Magnetic audiotape,Super-thin audiotape, 300 feet
  - Jenny Sweeting, undated; ID: 068.0097 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0097)
    Magnetic audiotape, unknown brand or length
  - David Rounds and Larry Anerbach, undated; ID: 068.0098 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0098)
  - Vyra and Louis, undated; ID: 068.0099 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0099)
  - June and Eddie, December 22, 1971 and Christmas 1971, #1, ID: 068.0100 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0100)
    Audiocassette, Realistic C-60
  - Dec. 23, 1971, June and Eddie on pot, #2, ID: 068.0101 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0101)